Did something happen between
you and that part-time guy?
A...
Actually, during one of our
breaks at work a while back,
Oji-kun asked me if I
could help him pick out a present
for his sister and so we went.
And while we were out...
He... confessed to me, and...
I did turn him down on the spot...
But I wasn't sure if I should
tell you about it...
So in the end, it came across
like I was trying to hide it,
so I'm sorry about that.
I see.
Got it.
Senpai... might be a little angry.
Well, of course he is.
I wish I'd just told him.
Wait...
Who did you hear this from?
Oh... Well, from the guy himself.
Wait, Oji-kun told you?
Well, the other day, when I
happened to go to your shop,
Yoshiko was with me.
And he took it the wrong way, and...
Uh...
Who's Yoshiko?
Shit...
No, no, Yoshiko and me aren't like that.
She's seriously just my childhood friend.
Please show me a picture of her.
Insta-worthy!
Ah!
My phone!
You came to my shop with a girl
I don't know when I wasn't around...
I really don't like that.
Actually, Yoshiko is
after your dad more than...
It doesn't matter!
It's not your place to talk, Senpai.
Yes it is.
Because I always put you first, Yoi-chan.
It's true that I went
to eat with Yoshiko,
but I'll introduce you to her
whenever you'd like.
I wasn't going to hide it.
During our summer break,
I figured it made sense that you'd
prioritize your friends.
But it makes me sad that when
you did have extra time,
you spent it with some other
guy and not me.
Oh...
I'm sorry, I...
It's fine.
You don't have to apologize.
I don't think you realize
it yourself, but...
The way you look when you're with him,
is a look that you've never shown me.
So if I'm being honest, if he were the
one who'd approached you first...
I think you would have gone
out with him instead.
Ow!
You idiot!
What? Hey.
Yoi-chan!
The nerve!
And to think I was so excited earlier.
I even gathered the courage
to go to his room!
The way he worded that,
as if I'd just go out with anyone...
It pisses me off and makes me so sad.
Every moment since I've started
dating Senpai has been so bright.
And yet, it turns out I was the only
one who felt we had something special.
I feel so stupid.
Ah... Damn it.
What the hell was I saying?
Oh...
Yoi-cha...
Good morning...?
Yoi-chan!
Wait, don't tell me you're not
wearing your contacts today?
Oh, yeah...
I didn't sleep much,
so my eyes are really dry.
Yoi-chan, are you all right?
Can you even see?
Slightly...
You've got this whole listless aura...
You didn't even do your hair.
I just didn't feel like it.
Oh, something definitely happened.
Is it even something we could ask about?
Hey, Ichi!
Kuwa, Sentaro!
We're gonna go eat ramen, right now!
Wha?
Nah, it's just past eight.
Is a place even open?
Chinese
Cuisine
Welcome in!
Your ramen's gonna get soggy.
Did something happen?
Wait, don't tell me it
went down like we said?
Huh, what? What went down?
Oh, no, it's nothing.
Y'know, I've always been the type
of guy who can bounce right back,
no matter how crappy I feel, just
by eating something I like.
But right now, I can't
even work up an appetite.
Yet you made us skip school for this?
Give us a break, man.
Sorry.
Now, now.
What?
Did you do something that made
the Prince angry at you again?
I did. And I said some awful stuff
without even thinking about it.
Truth is, I don't care about
Mr. Handsome.
He just happened to be the trigger,
and a petty complaint slipped out.
Summer
Festival
I want you to be completely
infatuated with me!
At some point, it felt like I
was the only one feeling this way.
So lame.
I mean, it's like...
Ever since I started dating Yoi-chan,
I feel like I'm really starting to
give off these "total loser" vibes.
Hey, Prince Loser!
You want to call it quits?
You want to stop and
move on to another girl?
Being the dry, lighthearted,
slick Prince Ichimura
just like old times?
Just like old times...
What was that like again?
Um!
Yoi Takiguchi-sama!
Here! Please accept this!
Oh... Uh...
Thank you.
Thank you so much for accepting it!
We're always rooting for you!
This was my norm before
I met Senpai, wasn't it?
What's this feeling?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Here's your gyoza.
Thanks.
Thanks for the grub!
Huh? You didn't finish.
Eat it for me.
But the bill...
I'll spot you next time.
Huh? What's up with him?
Huh?
A famous shop?
A popular one?
Did you really just call
me to ask about that?
Please.
Ever since I got her,
I've just come to want more and more.
I don't want her to hate me.
I don't want to cause her pain.
Today
Call ended 01:07
I want to touch her more.
I want to kiss her, too,
and even go beyond that.
I want her to feel the same way I feel.
I want her to...
fall for me...
even more!
Um, Yoi-san?
You already brought their
drinks a minute ago.
I'm so sorry!
Oh, no worries at all.
Yoi-san, did something happen?
I mean, you made a
lot of mistakes today, so...
Oh... Uh...
It's my fault, isn't it?
No, um...
I'm sorry.
Still...
I didn't want to keep silent,
if I knew the person I love
might get hurt.
I'm sorry for speaking out of turn,
after you already rejected me.
Uh...
It's hot, so let's lock up
and quickly head home.
Yes, let's.
So if I'm being honest, if he were the
one who'd approached you first...
I think you would have gone
out with him instead.
I wonder why I chose Senpai...
Oh!
It's the present from this morning!
I forgot I had it in my bag.
Are you all right?
Oh, I hope it didn't break.
It's so cute.
Is that a gift from someone?
Huh? Oh, yes...
Dear Yoi-sama,
When I saw this nail polish,
I thought it would look great on you,
so I decided to get it for you.
Before, I never pictured you
wearing things like nail polish.
But lately, I think you've become
incredibly cute, Yoi-sama!
And so, I intend to continue
admiring you from afar.
P.S.
Since it came out great,
I added a photo of you as well.
Huh? Isn't that covert photography?
Just beyond my gaze...
It's obvious who I'm staring at.
Jeez, I look just like a girl in love.
So this is the expression I wear.
I see.
The uneasy feeling I felt
this morning was from...
Compared to when I was
known as the "Prince"...
there's a girl who's shy,
and reserved,
and lazy,
and drafts contracts about everything...
and inside her head,
just like this nail polish,
there's a shower of
faint pink cherry blossoms.
Ever since I met Senpai,
I've felt more like my true self.
Yoi-san?
A lanky, slender build.
And a body that easily envelops it.
His deep voice...
His much deeper and sweeter voice...
Oh, gosh.
Right now, I...
desperately want to see Senpai!
Yoi-san...
Yoi-chan!
Senpai?
Um, what is it you want?
Sorry, handsome.
Yoi-chan is my girlfriend,
and you're in our way right now.
Huh?
H-Hey, um, Senpai?!
I'm sorry, could you lock up the shop?
H-Hey!
What was I thinking?
"Speaking out of turn,
after you already rejected me..."
After a scene like that,
I'm painfully reminded
of exactly where I stand.
All right!
Gonna go home and run ten kilometers!
Um! Hey, Senpai!
Where are we going?
Ow...
Here.
Sweets from a famous shop.
Also, this, and this, and this.
Huh, hey...
Um, why did you get so many sweets?
I've...
never been in a fight with a girl before.
So I don't exactly
know how to apologize.
I figured I'd boost my chances
by buying you a ton of sweets.
I'm sorry I said some
stupid shit and hurt you.
I know I was the one who said it,
but seeing you next to him just now...
Choco Anpan
I really didn't like it.
I'm sorry for being anxious and jealous,
and acting like a real loser.
I know it might look like I'm
trying to bribe you with gifts,
but I'm doing the best I can.
So, please stay by my side, Yoi-chan.
Seeing Senpai look so sweaty, flustered,
and totally uncool...
I've never seen him like this before.
Hey.
Yoi-san?
Y'know, this makes me super happy and all,
but I'm really sweaty right now.
What's a little sweat?
I'm sweaty, too.
Oh, all right.
You know you can't stand the heat.
And yet, there's stuff here that you
can't buy without waiting in a line...
That one, and that one...
Just to apologize for
something so small...
He's so stupid.
I'll have you know!
I gave it some serious
thought after what you said!
Y-Yeah...?
But it's not something I could
figure out just by thinking about it!
Besides, I wouldn't know what kind
of face I have when I'm with Oji-kun.
And it really bugged me that you
asked what I would have done
if someone else approached me first!
No, you're absolutely right.
But for some reason...
You're the only one who makes
me feel this way, Senpai, and...
even if it's just because I'm not used to
guys, what difference does that make?
I'm a tomboy, and I happened
to be in a place.
You happened to be there too.
We happened to run into each other,
got interested, and fell in love.
Can't that be enough?
Am I not allowed to call that fate?!
Damn.
I know I just did it,
but I feel like I could die happy.
J-Just now, did you—
Yep. I did.
Because...
When someone says something
that cool to you, you just gotta.
I want to be your fate, too, Yoi-chan.
Okay.
He and I...
We're not mortal enemies who fell in love.
We aren't on board a ship about to sink,
and the world's not going to end tomorrow.
It's just a love that happened to come
together based on chance and timing,
and maybe "fate" is too grand
a word for that, but...
Translation:
Timing:
Editing:
Quality Control:
Final Quality Control:
Yukari Murase-Louden
Andy Ellis
Gabriella Alabanza
Salem Alabanza
Elizabeth Ellis
IN THE CLEAR MOONLIT DUSK
To start, can we stop
by the convenience store?
Hmm?
No, it's nothing.
Even after doing something like that,
he just casually takes my hand.
And here I am, still feeling like
I'm floating on air.
Our small fight today.
The ton of sweets.
Senpai's slightly sweat-soaked shirt.
His big hand.
His sulky face.
The temperature of Senpai's lips.
For someone as insignificant as me,
it was all a big deal.
And I'll certainly never forget
about what happened today.